



Profile

I have been dealing with various software for about 10 years. In my early years I was involved with CMS systems (Opencart, WordPress etc). I have been working as a Frontend Developer with JavaScript, ReactJS (Redux), NodeJS, HTML, CSS and MongoDB for about 2 years.

Employment History

Front-End Developer at Freelance, Istanbul

2018 - Present

- I have been working in the e-commerce industry for 4 years
- I know the problems or the sector and produce solutions to these problems.
- Mastered e-commerce terminology by working in the field
- Systems I used throughout the process: Wordpress, Opencart and basic javascript, html and css

Front-End Developer (Intern) at ETurnsoft, Turkey

2022 - 2022

- Working on User Management System with admin panel.
- Using JavaScript, HTML, CSS, ReactJs, NodeJs, Bootstrap, and MongoDB



Education

Depertman of Economics at Karadeniz Teknical University, Trabzon 2010 - 2014

Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp (with Agile Tegnology), SoftInnovas Bootcamp, Istanbul

2021 - 2022



Courses

Full-Stack Javascript Development at SoftInnovas, Istanbul 2021 - 2022



The Books I Wrote

Dinozorlar Ülkesinde Çürümüş Bal Kabağı

First Edition - 2021 Publisher - Arines (9786058045743)

Details

Istanbul, Turkey +905301142548 halit.uzan@gmail.com

Links

Github : @halituzan Linkedin: @halituzan Portfolio: halituzan.github.io

Skills

Javascript HTML CSS ReactJs NodeJs MongoDB Git Opencart Wordpress Adobe Illustrator Adobe Photoshop

Languages

English (A2)

Hobbies

Camping, Fishing, Traveling, Flowers and Plants, to write